<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Products on Introduction</title>
    <link>https://joybountiful.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Products on Introduction</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://joybountiful.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Come, Follow Me Notebooks</title>
      <link>https://joybountiful.com/blog/come-follow-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joybountiful.com/blog/come-follow-me/</guid>
      <description>2019 marks a big change in the way that members of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints attend church and study the gospel. With the switch to a 2-hour meeting block, individuals and families have an exciting chance to study more at home.
This journal supports your personal or family home-centered plan for gospel learning and worship. In conjunction with Come, Follow Me—For Individuals and Families, weekly gospel study topics are listed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2018 T-shirts</title>
      <link>https://joybountiful.com/blog/oct2018shirts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joybountiful.com/blog/oct2018shirts/</guid>
      <description>This is a sample post. Want to display an image with a link to Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hipster Ipsum</title>
      <link>https://joybountiful.com/blog/hipster-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 11:58:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joybountiful.com/blog/hipster-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>Occupy mlkshk kale chips woke, listicle locavore next level fingerstache glossier aesthetic man braid before they sold out kitsch prism. Cred copper mug freegan, flannel YOLO single-origin coffee skateboard artisan four loko church-key man bun. Synth literally gastropub, kombucha chillwave helvetica offal truffaut church-key freegan pop-up gentrify narwhal. Kombucha viral vexillologist green juice. Slow-carb hoodie mumblecore tumeric tattooed meditation, lo-fi fap cred affogato forage whatever austin. Shabby chic direct trade migas, brunch gochujang sriracha chambray fanny pack 8-bit mustache letterpress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Ipsum</title>
      <link>https://joybountiful.com/blog/startup-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 12:04:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joybountiful.com/blog/startup-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>SpaceTeam affordances quantitative vs. qualitative SpaceTeam physical computing earned media thinker-maker-doer pair programming. Bootstrapping pitch deck physical computing driven cortado human-centered design innovate human-centered design driven. Grok pitch deck fund pitch deck sticky note affordances minimum viable product integrate paradigm viral iterate. Driven fund thought leader personas workflow SpaceTeam viral pair programming physical computing intuitive 360 campaign latte bootstrapping minimum viable product. Bootstrapping physical computing responsive pitch deck SpaceTeam parallax long shadow pitch deck bootstrapping ideate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Ipsum</title>
      <link>https://joybountiful.com/blog/coffee-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 12:04:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joybountiful.com/blog/coffee-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>Aromatic aroma con panna, crema so coffee robust coffee barista, café au lait trifecta that strong blue mountain cortado aftertaste. Aroma extraction french press, skinny sweet, blue mountain cup roast barista, beans, extra cappuccino mug crema strong. Americano caffeine white, con panna saucer sit, con panna eu, carajillo aftertaste kopi-luwak, body aftertaste cup single origin café au lait saucer. Macchiato java sweet arabica, turkish cup, eu flavour mug extraction white cortado saucer est white brewed instant, rich, barista breve cappuccino barista organic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>POPSOCKETS</title>
      <link>https://joybountiful.com/blog/popsockets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:42:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joybountiful.com/blog/popsockets/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journals</title>
      <link>https://joybountiful.com/blog/journals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joybountiful.com/blog/journals/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undated post</title>
      <link>https://joybountiful.com/blog/no-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joybountiful.com/blog/no-date/</guid>
      <description>I was born yesterday, tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>